# **Scott Caprisecca**

602-743-7811 | caprisecca@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> | Portfolio | GitHub

### Summary

I'm a front-end developer specializing in converting PSDs to responsive websites. I'm experienced with CSS frameworks as well as being able to code your project using HTML/CSS/JS. I am always continuing to learn more about web development and I am currently learning React, I look forward to using this in my next project.

#### **Technical Skills**

Front-end	HTML5, CSS3, SASS/SCSS, JavaScript, jQuery
Frameworks	Bootstrap, Bulma, Foundation (web and email)
UI/UX	Adobe XD, Photoshop
Source Control	Git, GitHub
Email Tools	Litmus, MailChimp, Hubspot

## **Projects**

#### Nauto Landing Page - View Site | View Code

Nauto is a fleet safety management and tracking system for AI vehicles. This is a landing page for their eBook offering more info on how to improve safety. This webpage is fully responsive and built using the Bulma framework.

#### Pour Wine & Taproom - View Website | View Code

Pour is a local pub in Mesa, AZ. I built this website for them using Bootstrap 4 and used Netlify for hosting. I focused on keeping this website simple, responsive and made the important info easy to find. I integrated <u>Untappd</u>, an app that lets customers know which beers are on tap, into the beer menu. I also set up <u>Tockify</u> on the events page to allow the owners to easily update their website.

#### Greer Lodge AZ - View Site | View Code

This is a promotional email for Greer Lodge in Arizona. This is a hand-coded HTML email, fully responsive and tested using Litmus.

## **Work Experience**

Hotfoot Recruiters | Recruiter July 2019 - Present

Allegis Global Solutions | Recruitment Sourcing Specialist

June 2017 - June 2019

### **Sharecare | Health Coach**

February 2016 - June 2017

### 1 Stop Recruiting | Senior Medical Recruiter

January 2015 - January 2016

## **Education**

Arizona State University
Bachelors of Science - Exercise Science